翻译  ET外星人
翻译  沫沫
翻译  TheWalkingNerd
翻译  江湖人称王姑娘
翻译  国士章鱼X
翻译  杏仁斯嘉丽
时间轴  壬虚浪影
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
第四季  第十二集
纸牌屋
人人影视倾情奉献
想要
成功
那就
讨论
一下
最近的
成绩
2016总统与副总统竞选辩论
哈里发帝国组织
国土安全部
急事
易卜拉欣·哈拉比  美穆关系协会会长
名字?
肯尼迪总统遇刺
林登·约翰逊宣誓就职
乔·沃勒克
劳拉·莫雷蒂
否则  这就是社会主义
Otherwise, it was just socialism,
那是注定要失败的
which is built to fail.
失败是不会为你加分的  总统先生
And you don't get points for failure, Mr. President.
人们不想要失败  他们要的是成功
People don't want failure. They want success.
那就讨论一下最近的功绩吧
Let's discuss our recent success then.
你一直指责总统
You have been very critical of the president
对恐怖活动的态度不够强硬
for not being strong on terror.
就在上周  特种部队逮捕了尤瑟夫·艾哈迈迪
Just last week, U.S. Special forces captured Yusuf Al Ahmadi,
并把他收监入狱
and they have him in custody.
那么你现在会不会说
So would you now say that
你对总统的指责是毫无根据的呢
your criticism of the president was unfounded?
对艾哈迈迪的逮捕是一个进步
The capture of Ahmadi is a step forward,
但真正的问题是长久的安全
but the real issue here is sustained security.
总统没跟叙利亚人打招呼
The president sent in American troops
就派出了美国军队
without consulting the Syrians.
那对我们日后与他们的合作
Now, that's gonna do real damage to our ability
将造成很大伤害
to work with them in the future.
重点不在于建功立业
See, this isn't about notches in a belt.
而是给我们国家以更安全的世界环境
It's about a safer world for our nation.
给我们的孩子一个更好的未来
A better future for our children.
州长  我明白"安全""孩子"等字眼
Governor, I understand that words like "safer"
有很好的效果
and "children" play well.
但国家安全是一个复杂且千变万化的领域
But national security is a complex and ever-changing landscape
有时也需要约束
that sometimes requires restraint,
有时也需要果断的行动
sometimes decisive action.
所以我觉得我们最好
So I think maybe we want to
放下眼前听起来不错的词
put aside what sounds good in the moment
现实一点讨论适合我们的政策
and be adaptable with our policy in terms of reality.
我不需要人教我什么是现实
Oh, I don't need a lecture on reality
好像我还是小男生似的  安德伍德夫人
like I'm a schoolboy, Mrs. Underwood.
我真正在中东打过仗
I've actually fought in the Middle East.
将军也是
So has the general.
我们对国际外交的观点并不只是花言巧语
Our views on international diplomacy aren't just pretty words.
我们可以如你所愿讨论政策  州长
We can debate policy all you'd like, Governor,
但有一件事不容置疑
but there is one thing that is undebatable.
那就是没有了领袖的哈里发国
And that is ICO is no longer the threat it once was
威胁性已不比从前
without their leadership.
你不看辩论吗
You're not watching the debate?
我知道他们要说什么
I know what they're going to say.
我能帮你什么  道格
How can I help you, Doug?
我告诉过你会有这么一天的
I told you there'd be a day.
你完全可以带着这些光荣退休
There's no reason you shouldn't keep this and retire with honor.
情况如何
How are we looking?
"千变万化"很有冲击力
Yeah, high impact on "ever-changing."
康威上钩了
And Conway took the bait
连"小男生"和"花言巧语"都出来了
and played right into "schoolboy" and "pretty",
合起来就是"可爱男生"  太美妙了
which gives you "pretty boy." It was beautiful.
婚姻的事怎么样
What about the marriage stuff?
他们越是反复在任何语境中
Well, the more they can keep saying
说"一起"  "超越"
"together" and "beyond" and "become"
和"成为"  我们都加分
in any context, we score on those.
我不会跟你讨论
I don't discuss the private conversations
我们情报委员会的私下谈话
we have on the Intelligence Committee.
告密会让你孤立无援
Whistle-blowing insulates you.
那就给我党提名人拆台吗
And kneecap my party's nominee?
休想
I don't think so.
他会在这次辩论中说谎
He's going to lie about it at this debate.
他们都会
They both are.
你只是说出真相
You're going to tell the truth.
你不能二者兼得  州长
You can't have it both ways, Governor.
我们抓到他了  结束
We got him, period.
这是单方面  目光短浅的行为
Unilateral, short-sighted action.
单方面是因为你和将军
Unilateral because you and the general
让共和党就跟俄罗斯人合作的事反对我
pitted the Republicans against my involving the Russians.
那是无稽之谈
That's just not true.
你是说你没有
Are you saying that you did not
让将军跟众议院情报委员会的人联系吗
have the general contact members of the House Intelligence Committee?
将军  你愿意评论一下吗
General, would you care to comment?
我辞去职务后
When I resigned my commission,
就不再跟国会的人
I stopped talking to members of Congress
谈论国家安全事宜了
about matters of national security.
那么你是说你没有吗
So you are saying that you did not?
不  女士  我没有
No, ma'am. I did not.
你我都知道你插手了  州长
You and I both know that you interfered, Governor.
我私下问你的时候  你都承认了
You admitted so much to me when I asked you personally.
你跟我说将军
You told me that the general
曾跟委员会的成员谈过
had spoken to members of that committee.
我跟你说的是我在委员会有朋友
I told you that I have friends on the committee,
那是真的
which is true.
而不是我干涉了委员会的工作
Not that I interfere with committee work.
你让每个共和党人
You lined up every Republican
都反对俄罗斯入局
to be opposed to the Russians being involved.
他们都一致反对了
It was unanimous opposition.
如果你打算放弃钻井
Well, if your plan was to get Russian support
以获得俄罗斯的支持  我不怪他们
by giving away drill sites, I don't blame them.
那我们明确一下
So just to be absolutely clear, for the record,
州长  你是说
you are saying, Governor,
你本人或是将军都没有联系过
that neither you nor the General made any contact
众议院情报委员会的任何成员吗
with any member of the House Intelligence Committee?
我绝对没有
I absolutely did not.
你这是让我左右为难
You're putting me in an impossible place here.
你伪造服役记录时就将自己置于这种境地了
You put yourself there when you lied about your service record.
你想曝光谁的谎言
Whose lie do you want exposed?
康威的还是你自己的
Conway's or yours?
回家想一想
Go home and think about it.
不用赶在明天
Doesn't need to happen tomorrow.
只要在选举日之前就行
It just needs to happen before Election Day.
我不是想抹煞你对于你丈夫
I'm not trying to diminish your contribution
总统工作的贡献  安德伍德夫人
to your husband's presidency, Mrs. Underwood,
但我对你的经验表示质疑
but I do question your experience.
没有人在当上总统时
No one's fully prepared to be President
就充分准备好了
when he or she becomes one.
你也不能
Not even you.
看看民调结果
And look at the polls.
全国支持第一夫人做副总统的选民过半
Over half the country is open to a First Lady as VP.
想要一位新总统的选民也过半
And more than half of the country wants a new president.
你确实在民调中暂时领先  州长
It's true that you are leading in the polls for now, Governor,
但近几周内  差距正在缩小
but the gap has been closing in recent weeks.
当人们前去投票
Well, when people show up to vote
不得不面对克莱尔·安德伍德
and have to confront the possibility
成为总统的可能性
of Claire Underwood as President,
他们就要摸摸良心  做出正确的选择
they're gonna have a gut check and make the right choice.
说得非常对  那意味着他们会投给我们
You're absolutely right. That means they'll vote for us.
因为他们想想就会发现
Because they'll look around and realize
如果我出了什么事
that if anything happens to me,
他们能放心让克莱尔接手
they'll be in very good hands with Claire.
而且她说得对
And, you know, she's right.
没人能在做总统前完全准备好
No one can prepare to become the president.
而我已经是总统了
But I have been the President,
现在我知道那需要什么
and now I know what it takes.
需要的是信心  坦诚和效力
It requires confidence, openness, effectiveness,
而克莱尔具备所有这些品质
and Claire has all of those qualities.
很抱歉  总统先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President. It...
似乎我们得暂停一下
It looks like we have to take a break.
我们稍后将继续进行史上首次
We'll return shortly to the first-ever simultaneous debate
总统候选人和竞选搭档的同场辩论
between presidential candidates and their running mates.
已停
And we're clear.
总统先生  安德伍德夫人
Mr. President, Mrs. Underwood,
两位请跟我来一下好吗
would you please come with me?
念出来
Read it.
什么
What?
"我们是美国公民
"We are citizens of the United States.
我们被哈里发帝国组织  以真主之名
We have been taken hostage in the name of God
作为人质扣押"
by the Islamic Caliphate Organization."
念出来
Read it.
"我们国家犯下了非法侵略
"Our country is guilty of illegal aggression
和大规模屠杀穆斯林的罪行
and mass murder against Muslims.
我们恳求宽恕"
We beg for mercy."
只有满足以下要求  哈里发国才会给予宽恕
ICO will grant mercy only if these demands are met.
一  停止美军在叙利亚的一切军事行动
One, cessation of all U.S. Military activity in Syria.
二  向哈里发支付一百亿美元赔偿
Two, ten billion dollars in reparations paid to the Caliphate.
三  安全送还我们遭到
Three, the safe return of our leader,
不公正囚禁的领导人  尤瑟夫·艾哈迈迪
Yusuf Al Ahmadi, from his unjust imprisonment.
我们不会和罪犯弗兰克·安德伍德沟通
We will not communicate with the criminal Frank Underwood.
我们只和他的继任者威廉·康威沟通
We will only communicate with his successor, William Conway.
如未能在24小时内满足以上要求
If these demands aren't met in 24 hours...
将不予以宽恕
mercy will not be granted.
视频在七个渠道上发布
Released to seven outlets.
通过加密邮件和暗网
Encrypted email, Deep Web.
三名人质是吉姆和卡洛琳·米勒夫妇
The hostages are Jim and Caroline Miller,
和女儿梅莉莎  是诺克斯维尔人
their daughter Melissa, from Knoxville.
总统先生  不论你需要什么
Mr. President, whatever you need,
我愿意提供帮助
I'm here to offer assistance.
我会告知你的
I'll let you know.
我们目前识别出了板墙和照明设备
So far, we've identified the drywall and lighting.
都是美国制造的
All U.S. Manufactured.
视频是用松下高清摄影机录制
The video was shot on a Panasonic HD camcorder,
在美国销量最大
most widely sold in the States.
所以可以确定他们在国内
So we know they're in the country.
民航班机可以排除
Well, commercial flight is out.
私人飞机不太可能
Private plane is unlikely.
我们很肯定他们是乘坐陆地交通
We're confident that they traveled by ground,
可能是米勒家被劫持的汽车
probably the Millers' hijacked car.
最后已知地点是诺克斯维尔市外一家丹尼餐厅
Last known location is a Denny's just outside of Knoxville.
一笔借记卡交易
A debit card transaction.
这是他们离开餐厅的影像
This is footage of them leaving the restaurant.
我们心系米勒一家人及其亲友
Our hearts go out to the Millers' family and loved ones.
但我们相信总统
But we're confident that the President
正在尽一切可能营救他们
is doing everything possible to achieve their release.
我告诉总统  我们愿意
I told the President that we'd be willing
提供任何协助
to assist in any way if it would be helpful.
此时此刻美国必须团结一致并...
This is a time when America needs to pull together and...
暂停
Stop.
是"团结一致并为米勒一家人祈祷"
It's "pull together and pray for the Millers."
-然后再换我...  -我没忘词
- And then I come in, and-- - I didn't forget.
我只是认为这样做不对
I just feel this is wrong.
此举暗示我们愿意与恐怖分子谈判
It implies we're willing to negotiate with terrorists.
我们该保持沉默
We should keep our mouths shut.
让当权者去做他们的工作
Let the authorities do their job.
保持沉默不会为我们获得新闻版面
We don't get press by keeping our mouths shut.
你已经让我在全国节目上说谎
You had me lie on national television.
现在还要我们发布这种
And now you want us to send out some video
只会刺激恐怖分子的视频
that only encourages these people?
而且这么做只为博得版面
And you wanna do that to score some press coverage?
如果你认为这么做不妥
If it doesn't make you feel comfortable,
我可以自己来
I can do it on my own.
我在外面等
I'll be outside.
我受够他了
I've had enough of him.
他说的确实有道理
He does have a point.
无论我们是否发布这视频
Look, they're gonna kill that family
他们都会杀害那一家人
whether we send this out or not.
我们还不如说我愿意尽义务出面
We might as well say I was willing to show up for duty.
我必须说  我同意将军的看法
Well, I have to say, I agree with the General.
开始录像
Press record.
Press record!
我们心系米勒一家人及其亲友
Our hearts go out to the Millers' family and loved ones...
关于劫持者我们掌握了什么信息
What do we know about the captor?
我们叙利亚的线人说这是起单独行动
Our Syrian assets say this is a lone wolf.
实际上  是两人的行动
Two wolves, actually.
我们调高了视频的对比度后
When we pumped up the contrast in the video,
在墙上发现了一个从摄影机后投射出的人影
we saw a shadow on the wall from someone behind the camera.
语音分析认为歹徒来自田纳西州西孟菲斯地区
Voice analysis points to western Tennessee, Memphis area.
总统先生  我能说几句吗
Uh, Mr. President, if I may?
霍尔布鲁克探员  我们的顶尖谈判专家
Agent Holbrooke, our top negotiating expert.
我们针对这种事件进行过
Uh, we've run 16 possible models in preparation
16种情况模拟
for an incident like this.
目前的事件包含三种情况的关键因素
Now, what we have here are key elements from three of them.
美国绑架犯  儿童遭绑架
American kidnappers, the abduction of a child
以及要求沟通代理人
and proxy communication...
他们为什么指名康威
Why did they want Conway?
这才是重点  我告诉你为什么
That's the real question. I'll tell you why.
因为换做是我  我也会这么做
Because I would've done exactly the same thing if it had been me.
这能削弱我的权威
It undermines my authority.
让我措手不及  挑起对立
Throws me off balance. Pits me against my rival.
还因为我没有孩子  而康威有
And because I don't have children, and he does.
他们知道我不会妥协
They know I won't compromise.
没有总统会妥协
No president would.
但康威这样的总统候选人  或许会妥协
But a would-be president like Conway, well, he might.
战术上我们需要更多时间
Tactically, we need more time.
我无法保证我们
I can't guarantee that we can
24小时内能追踪到他们
track them down in less than 24 hours.
够了  我的计划是这样的
Enough. Here's what I wanna do.
总统正与联调局
The president is working with the FBI
及其他执法和情报部门合作
and other law enforcement and intelligence agencies
寻找米勒一家
to locate the Millers.
为了确保这些行动不受干扰
Now, in order to protect the integrity of those efforts,
我目前无法透露任何行动的具体进展
I won't be sharing any details on their progress at the moment.
同时  总统还寻求康威州长的支援
In the meantime, the president is reaching out to Governor Conway
为一旦与劫持者建立了联系作准备
should contact with the captors be established.
有一点我要说清
Now, let me be clear.
这并不是谈判
We're not talking about negotiation,
只是沟通
just communication.
你大可先私下问我
You could've asked me privately first.
这是战略  向劫持者显示
It was tactical, to show the kidnappers
我们尊重他们的要求
that we respect their wishes.
这让我别无选择
This doesn't leave me a choice.
你可以拒绝嘛  州长
Well, you can always say no, Governor.
我们已有一份计划
We have a plan for how we can
即使没有你的参与也能处理
handle this without your participation.
那要怎么进行
How would that work?
我会公开表示
Well, I say publicly that
我愿意亲自与劫持者谈
I'm willing to speak to the captors myself.
如果他们拒绝
Now, if they refuse,
我们得做最坏的打算
we'd have to be prepared for the worst.
但我们团队相信
But our team believes that
有你在  我们建立对话的机会比较大
you give us a better shot at opening a dialogue.
好谈判
To negotiate.
好为我们争取时间
To buy us time.
如果你答应
And if you do say yes,
我们希望你尽快到白宫来
we'd want you at the White House as soon as possible.
我需要和我的团队讨论
I need to discuss with my people.
我希望你会同意协助我们
I'm hoping that you'll agree to help us.
无论如何  我尽快需要答复
Either way, I'll need an answer soon.
我了解  一小时内会给你回复
I understand. I'll let you know within the hour.
谢谢  州长
Thank you, Governor.
每个人都有缺点  而这就是康威的缺点
Everyone has a flaw, and this is Conway's.
我和总统谈过  我说
I spoke with the president, and I said that
我愿提供任何协助
I'm willing to assist in any way if it would be helpful.
他渴望聚光灯
He aches for the spotlight.
否则他几乎感觉自己是隐形的
He feels almost invisible without it.
如果他在这个舞台的中央
Now, if he's center stage on this,
他就不能挑我的刺
he can't fault my performance,
因为我们要共享这个舞台
because we're sharing the stage together.
如果我被喝倒彩  他就也被喝倒彩
If I get booed, he gets booed.
但康威渴望的其实是掌声
But it's really the applause that Conway's hungry for.
相信我  他会同意的
Trust me, he'll say yes.
舞台太大
The stage is too big
灯光太过诱人
and the spotlight too tempting
他受不了...仅仅当一个观众
for him to be... a mere spectator.
但我已经公开声明如果他需要我会协助
But I've already said publicly I'd assist if he asked.
那是个错误
That was a mistake,
我应该更努力阻止的
and I should've pushed back on it more.
但你不能让他利用你
But you can't let him take advantage of it.
我说都说了
Well, I've said it. It's done.
现在我们得往前走
And now we have to move forward.
这玩意真难喝
This is fucking disgusting.
你说  "经过慎重考虑
You say, "After much consideration,
我不愿意与恐怖分子谈判"
I don't feel comfortable negotiating with terrorists."
那我不仅成了一个骗子
And then I come off not only as a liar,
还是个懦夫
but as a coward.
我们都领先了  为什么要这么做
Why do this when we're ahead?
领先多少  5个百分点  那不是领先
By what? Five points? That's not a lead.
是碰运气
That's a coin toss.
整场竞选我传达的信息
My message this entire campaign
就是为国家服务  承担责任
has been about serving the country, showing up for duty,
现在三军统帅要我帮忙
and now I'm gonna not show up when the Commander-in-Chief
我却拒绝吗
has asked for my help?
...语言模式
...and the speech patterns.
劫持者是视频中说话的人
The captor is the one who you heard on the camera.
似乎是美国人
Seems to be American.
从他公布视频的方式可以看出来
And the way he's released the video shows
他是个电脑行家
he's computer savvy.
哈里发国招募人员已转向使用社交网络
Now, ICO recruiters have been turning to social media networks
比如脸书  推特  图片分享
like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram,
和那些认同支持他们事业的用户取得联系
to initiate contact with users sympathetic to their cause.
-汤姆  -之前的组织  如基地组织
- Oh, Tom. - Earlier groups, like al-Qaeda,
使用社交网络的程度
didn't use social networking
均远远不及哈里发国
anywhere near the degree that ICO has.
劫持者有可能...
It is possible that this captor...
-总统先生  -飞行顺利吗
- Mr. President. - Good flight?
-有点颠簸  不过还好  -进来吧
- A little bumpy, but fine. - Come on in.
你弹吗
You play?
这个有待争论
Well, that's debatable.
但我确实收集
But I definitely collect.
这是个大事
Uh, this is something.
是啊  太可怕了
Yeah, it's terrible.
我不羡慕此刻的弗兰克
I don't envy Frank right now.
请坐
Have a seat.
-喝咖啡还是茶  -不用了  谢谢
- Coffee? Tea? - No, thanks.
发生了这么多事
I appreciate you taking the time,
我很感激你愿腾出时间见我
given everything that's going on.
反正又没人打电话寻求我的建议
It's not as though anyone's calling for my advice.
但这篇文章目前似乎没那么重要
Although I'm not sure this article is pertinent at the moment.
我不是来谈你的奖学基金的
I'm not here about your scholarship fund.
我不明白了  我的助理说你想写...
I don't understand. My assistant said you wanted to write--
我撒谎了...好让你肯见我
I lied... so you'd meet with me.
我们有国内监控项目  处于调试阶段
We have a domestic surveillance program, beta phase,
目标是找出哈里发国招募的人
aimed at finding ICO recruits.
外国情报监视法法庭裁决下来时我听到了汇报
I was briefed when we got the FISA court ruling.
这是国内调查
Well, this is a domestic investigation.
我们必须通过联调局工作
We have to work through the FBI.
他们准备派出一支队伍
Now, they're sending over a team,
我希望国土安全部和中情局加入
and I'd like for Homeland and the CIA to join them.
这事很敏感  你不应该关起门办事吗
This is a sensitive program. Shouldn't you keep it in-house?
我们过去曾因不让别的机构加入而受批评
We've been criticized for not involving other agencies in the past.
我想避免这个
I'd like to avoid that.
-你想要安全许可  -越快越好
- You want clearances? - As soon as possible.
事情紧急  需要齐心协力  道格
It's all hands on deck, Doug.
-州长  -总统先生
- Governor. - Mr. President.
这位一定是查理了
Well, and this must be Charlie.
-查理...  -和总统握手  查理
- Charlie... - Shake the President's hand, Charlie.
-来呀  查理  -你说他是个吸血鬼
- Come on, Charlie. - You said he was a vampire.
别担心  你在这儿很安全
Well, don't worry. You're safe here.
白宫里没有妖怪
No monsters in the White House.
我带你们去住的地方
I'll show you where you're staying.
好的  走吧  查理
Okay. Come on, Charlie.
你去过总统办公室吗
Have you ever been in the Oval?
小时候去过一次
Once, when I was a kid.
童子军  我们见了里根
My Boy Scout troop, we met with Reagan.
当然了
Of course they did.
我想你们会想住在一起
I thought you'd all like to be together,
所以安排在了这里
so I've put you in here,
如果不想  我们可以让孩子住林肯卧室
but, if not, we can put the kids in the Lincoln Bedroom.
不用了  这儿太棒了  谢谢
No, this is wonderful. Thank you.
我们以后就要住这里吗  妈妈
Is this where we're gonna live, Mommy?
那得看大选的结果了
We'll have to see how the election goes first.
有股臭味儿
Something smells.
天啊  莉莉需要换尿布了
Oh, gosh. Lily needs a change.
请问哪里有...
Um, where--
从这儿往右走就是卫生间
The restroom is here, to the right.
太好了  谢谢
Great, thank you.
你想让我把一个共和党人送进白宫
You want me to put a Republican in the White House.
你是想要一个共和党  还是一个罪犯
You want a Republican or a criminal?
我对党还是忠诚的  汤姆
I still have loyalty to my party, Tom.
那他们对你的忠诚呢
And where's their loyalty?
他们都打算弹劾你了
They were going to impeach you.
杰姬·夏普说服了民主党
Jackie Sharp whipped Democrats.
你的国务卿也背弃了你
Your own Secretary of State turned her back.
你的党  已经烂到核心了
Your party? It's rotten to the core.
而那个核心  就是安德伍德
And the core is Underwood.
他偷了你的总统之位你就不生气吗
Aren't you angry that he stole your presidency?
我当然生气
I'm angry.
我气我自己
I'm angry at myself...
没能料到
for not seeing it.
还气我没和他斗到底
And for not fighting it.
那就现在反击吧
So do something now.
我本来想说塔斯克撒谎了
I wanted to say Tusk lied.
但是得到特赦后  我知道没人会相信我
But once I got the pardon, I knew nobody would believe me.
我就想
I thought...
"消失吧  躲得远远的"
"Just disappear. Go away."
而那种愤怒
And that anger...
如果我退隐了
If I went away...
那股怒气也会消失
that anger would go away.
真相要曝光了
The truth is coming out.
一起来揭露吧
Be part of the truth.
民众会相信你的
People will believe you.
等媒体发布会一结束  你的任务就完成了
Once we finish with the press conference, you'll be done.
后面交给我们就好
We'll take it from there.
如果他们联系我们  你不需要我接电话吗
You don't want me on the call if they contact us?
你的任务只是把他们引出来  州长
Oh, you're only there for bait, Governor.
我不能让你代表白宫和他们谈判
I can't have you speaking on behalf of the White House.
他们说了想和我交涉
They said they wanted me.
没错  但我们有计划了
Yes, we have a roadmap in place.
那就调整一下吧
Then you'll have to adjust it.
你有什么资格大摇大摆走进来
What right do you have to walk in here
对我们的应对方案指手画脚
and dictate how we're gonna handle this?
我来也是担了风险的  这你知道
I put myself on the line coming here, and you know it.
我大可撒手不管  让你自己焦头烂额去
I could've backed off and left this pile of shit in your lap.
如果我要和你一起出镜
Now, if I'm gonna be exposed with you,
那我对谈判方案就得有发言权
then I'm gonna have some say in how that happens.
要不我就回纽约  看着你出丑
Or I head back to New York and watch you squirm.
正中我下怀
Just as I'd hoped.
他搀和得越深越好
The more involved, the better.
请接格林处长
Director Green, please.
他们来了吗
They here?
-来了  -多谢
- They're here. - Thanks.
这是我们局长
This is our director.
-你好  -这是总统幕僚长
- Hello. - President's Chief of Staff.
我们需要过去三天内所有
We need every white male under 40
活动范围不正常的40岁以下白人男性的资料
with geo-local anomalies in the past 72 hours.
已整理好了  也和你们的监视名单核对过了
Already done that, cross-referenced with your watchlists.
我们正在匹配电话语音
We're voice matching with phone calls now.
我们会派一支队伍进驻
Well, we're bringing a team in here.
联调局  中情局  国安部和我们的人
FBI, CIA, Homeland, along with our own people.
同时参与的人太多只会...
Uh, yeah, more cooks in the kitchen won't--
我已经给他们权限了
I've cleared them.
我们不能在沟通上耽误时间
We can't waste time grapevining this.
让大家坐在一起工作
Let's get everyone working from the same place.
我们需要组织工作流程
We need to organize workflow.
好  我们去我办公室谈
Right. Uh, let's talk in my office.
往右第二间就是
It's the second door on the right.
会有问题吗
Is this going to be a problem?
我更希望他们不要监视我工作
I'd prefer them not breathing down my neck.
我问的不是这个
That wasn't my question.
我说了  都掩盖好了
I told you, we're masked.
谢谢  请坐
Thank you. Please be seated.
我想感谢康威州长同意来协助我们
I'd like to thank Governor Conway for agreeing to assist us.
他和我的目标是一致的
He and I share the same goal,
就是让米勒一家安全回家
which is the safe return of the Millers.
为实现这一目的
In order to achieve that,
我们将和劫持者
we're willing to open up lines
通过专线进行交涉
of communication with their captors.
州长
Governor.
我将作为你和总统之间的调解人
I will act as intermediary between you and the president.
想和我们联系
To communicate with us,
只需依次拨打吉姆和卡洛琳·米勒的社保号
dial Jim Miller's social security number followed by Caroline's
使用任何手机或网络运营商都可以
into any phone or Internet conferencing service.
然后将会有语音识别提示
There will be a voice recognition prompt.
让米勒一家念出自己的名字和即时时间
Have all three Millers say their names and state the time
连线即会建立
and that will connect you.
我们心系米勒一家和他们的亲属
Our hearts are with the Millers and their families.
我昨晚和他们的亲人通了话
I spoke to their siblings and their parents last night,
他们还在坚持着
and they remain strong.
我呼吁全体国民  为了他们  保持坚强
And I would ask all Americans to remain strong on their behalf.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
虽然眼下情势非常险恶
Deplorable as this situation is,
但我们不能怪罪全体伊斯兰人士
we cannot blame Islam as a whole
也不应牵连国内渴望和平的数百万穆斯林
or the millions of Muslims in our nation who yearn for peace,
他们为我们的社会辛勤奉献
who contribute to our society,
和所有美国人共享一个美国梦
who have the same dreams as all Americans do.
哈里发国不能代表伊斯兰
ICO does not represent Islam.
但是某些别有用心的人会利用这次事件
But there are those who would use this incident
为采取强硬措施寻找借口
to justify draconian measures,
比如出行限制或强制注册等
like travel restrictions or forced registration,
他们这是在鼓吹仇恨  甚至暴力
who would espouse hatred or even violence.
一旦爱国走上了偏执的歧路
The moment bigotry becomes a form of patriotism,
美国就不再是美国了
America is no longer America.
所以我今天来到国会
That is why I'm here today, in the Capitol,
呼吁各位众议员
to urge our congressmen and women...
听说有人支持筹赎金
Hear there's a push to get the ten billion.
财政委员会吵翻了天
Big debate in Ways and Means,
但是绝对到不了众议院表决
but it'll never make it to the floor.
装装样子而已
It's just for show.
我一直在和拨款委员会谈
I've been with Appropriations.
-想绕过财政委吗  -不是
- Bypass Ways and Means? - No.
为向叙利亚派地面部队增兵作拨款准备
To pay for more ground troops in Syria if we need them.
那为什么约我来这里  而不是在国会
So why are you meeting me instead of at the Capitol?
汤姆·汉默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
他也联系你了吗
Has he called you, too?
联系了  但我什么都没说
He reached out, but I haven't said a word.
沃克公开声明了
Walker went on record.
告诉他是我发动本党议员弹劾他
Told him I was the one who whipped the votes for impeachment.
你的说辞就是你认为他有罪
Your story is you thought he was guilty.
这没什么不对的
There's nothing wrong with that.
这么说你和他谈过了
So you have talked to him?
他有几个推论
He has some theories.
我只是把他想错的地方澄清了
All I did was shake my head at the parts that weren't right.
你不开口  就不会担责任
You're clean if you don't talk.
我想开口  接受他采访
I want to. On the record.
我认为你也该这样
I think you should, too.
我们不行
We can't.
那些照片一泄露  你的众议员席位就不保了
You will lose your seat as soon as those photos are leaked.
反正也快保不住了
I may lose my seat anyway.
康威的超级政治行动委员会
Conway's super PAC is targeting
在针对所有选情严峻的加州民主党参选人
every California Democrat in a tight race.
就算我赢了  国会也是共和党占多数
Even if I win, I'm in a Republican-controlled Congress
总统也是共和党人
with a Republican president...
要不就是再给安德伍德当四年走狗
or I have to do Underwood's bidding for the next four years.
那艾伦呢
What about Alan?
我把我们的事告诉他了
I told him about us.
他挺大度的
He was kind about it.
等事情消停了  我们就离婚
We'll divorce once everything quiets down.
如果你不希望照片流出  那我不开口就是了
If you don't want the photos out there, I won't say anything.
我不在乎全世界怎么议论我
I don't care about what the rest of the world thinks of me.
我只想保护你
All I cared about was protecting you.
那我们站出来吧  雷米
Then let's do this, Remy.
只要我们站出来  他就完了
You and I go on the record, he's done.
约书亚·马斯特森  田州理工计算科学专业
Joshua Masterson. Computer science major at Tennessee Tech.
过去两年一直热衷于研究
Taken a keen interest in Islamic studies
和伊斯兰教有关的事
during the past two years.
连续翘课三天
Hasn't been to class in three days.
也没有与亲友联系
None of his friends or family have heard from him.
他的声音和视频里的匹配
Voice matches the one in the video.
我们判断他的同伙是扎克瑞·霍松
We believe his associate is Zachary Hawthorne,
高中辍学  和马斯特森关系很近
high school dropout who's remained close with Masterson.
上周二开始翘班
Stopped showing up for work last Tuesday.
等他们打来  我应该...
So if they call, should I...
我要表明我们知道他们的身份吗
should I tell them that we know who they are?
不  你只要自我介绍就行  州长
No, you'll introduce yourself, Governor,
然后介绍我来接手对话
then you introduce me.
不  让州长和他们交涉
No, the governor will do the talking,
他到底能不能用他们的名字
so should he use their names or not?
这可能会刺激他们做出冲动之举
It could cause them to do something rash.
玛奇探员是我们的首席心理学家
Agent March, our head psychologist.
所以我不能提
So I shouldn't.
但反过来说  这或许能使他们回归常人
Conversely, it could humanize them.
消除匿名给他们的信心
Removes the confidence of anonymity.
但如果他们因此逃跑  那就坏事了
But if they run, it compromises everything.
不止如此  我们确信这就是他们的身份
Not just that. We're confident on the IDs,
但还是有极微小的可能猜错了人
but if there's the slightest chance we're wrong,
那就会削弱我们在谈判中的地位
it weakens our position.
那电话里先别提他们的名字了
Then don't use their names in the call.
先生  我们的对话脚本
Uh, sir, our script is written
是以我作为交涉人撰写的
with the understanding that I'd be speaking.
我们还需要为州长重新调整
We'd have to rework it for the governor.
那马上进行调整
Well, then let's rework it now.
我们不知道他们什么时候会打来
We don't know when they'll be calling.
虽然现在的情况很糟糕
You know, the circumstances are awful,
但我还是得承认
but I have to admit...
能从竞选中解脱一小会儿真是太棒了
it's been nice to take a break from the road.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you do it,
同时当竞选搭档和第一夫人
running mate and First Lady.
事实上我自己也在琢磨呢
I'm still trying to figure that out myself, actually.
我觉得这令人敬佩
I think it's admirable.
如果我们赢了
If we win,
我想做点更新图片分享之外的事
I'd love to do something more than update my Instagram.
我当时批评那个  只是...
When I criticized that, it was just because--
不  没关系  我不介意
No, not at all. I didn't take offense.
这是政治
It's politics.
我想做点类似你枪支法案那样的事
I'd love to do something like your gun bill.
没能通过参议院真是遗憾
It's a shame it didn't pass the Senate.
你支持那项立法
You support that legislation?
我来自英格兰
Mmm, I'm from England.
我们认为你们对枪支的痴迷太疯狂了
We think your gun obsession is madness.
威尔也是  但是他不能承认
Will does, too, but he can't admit it.
-不能惹怒中坚选民  -对呀  中坚选民
- Mustn't upset the base. - Ah, yes, the base.
不能惹怒中坚选民
Mustn't upset the base.
你其实是我的榜样
You know, you're actually a role model of mine.
你做的那些工作  环保
I mean, your work on the environment,
性侵犯  当大使...
sexual assault, being ambassador...
当然了  我更想我们赢
I mean, obviously, I'd prefer if we win.
但如果赢不了
But if we didn't,
你一定能成为一名优秀的副总统
I think you'd make a wonderful Vice President.
妈妈  你在喝什么
Mommy, what are you drinking?
是咖啡  亲爱的
It's coffee, sweetheart.
我也想要  我也想要
I want some! I want some!
别这么大声  会吵醒妹妹的
Not so loud. You'll wake your sister.
我能喝一点吗
Can I have some?
你还太小了
You're not old enough.
你想喝水吗  或是果汁
But do you want some water or some juice?
冰箱里应该有果汁
I think we've got some juice in the fridge.
我去拿
I'll get it.
他好可爱
He's very cute.
你后悔没要孩子吗
Do you regret it, not having children?
对不起  这个问题太私人了
Oh, I'm sorry. That's too personal.
那你后悔过要孩子吗
Do you ever regret having them?
声音已经确认了  他们在线上  先生
We've got voice verification. They're on the line, sir.
我需要拖住他们好让你们追踪通话吗
Do I need to keep them engaged so you can trace the call?
不用  是网络通话
No, Internet call.
每30毫秒换路由  无法追踪
Rerouted every three milliseconds. Untraceable.
我们有两个主要目标
We have two main objectives.
获取更多信息  拖延最后期限
More information, extending the deadline.
但最重要的是证明人质还活着
But our top priority is a first concession. Proof of life.
所以你什么都别承诺
So you'll promise nothing.
好
Okay.
记住他们可能会对通话录音
Keep in mind that they may be recording this call.
他们想要炒作
It's publicity they want.
好  我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
我是康威州长
This is Governor Conway.
我想和吉姆  卡洛琳和梅莉莎通话
I'd like to speak with Jim, Caroline and Melissa.
你和我说
You speak to me.
我需要证据证明他们还活着
I need some proof that they're still alive.
请告诉梅莉莎她的祖父母非常想念她
Please tell Melissa that her grandparents miss her very much
他们在为她祈祷
and, uh, they are praying for her.
你这么做不会让我们为他们感到抱歉
You're not gonna make us feel sorry for 'em.
你向无辜的穆斯林
How sorry did you feel
投炸弹的时候  又有多抱歉  州长
when you dropped bombs on innocent Muslims, Governor?
总统是个懦夫  派别人去替他杀人
The President's a coward. He sends others to do his killing.
但你更坏
But you're worse.
你还发表讲话说你对打了一场不义之战
You make speeches about how proud you are
感到多么的自豪
that you fought in an unjust war.
如果炸弹落在你女儿身上  你会是什么感受
How would you feel if a bomb was dropped on your daughter?
如果她被炸飞  死无全尸
If she was blown up and had to be buried in pieces?
你是美国人  对吗
You're American, right?
我们效忠于尤瑟夫·艾哈迈迪
Our allegiance is to Yusuf Al Ahmadi
和哈里发帝国
and the Islamic Caliphate.
美国是我们的敌人  必须满足我们的要求
America is our enemy and must meet our demands.
你知道
Uh, you understand that
我不能代表政府说话
I can't speak on behalf of the government.
我只能把你说的话转达给总统
I can only communicate what you say to the President.
我需要些时间
I'll need some time.
你当我们傻吗  他正听着呢
You think we're stupid? He's listening right now.
我是总统
This is the President speaking.
我们只和康威说话
We talk to Conway only.
如果你想要什么的话
But if you want anything to happen,
只有我能办到
I'm the one that can make it so.
那你为什么什么都不做
Then why have you done nothing?
我在和国会讨论赎金的事
I'm talking to Congress about the money.
和我的军事顾问讨论撤军
I'm consulting with my military advisers about a pullout,
但这些都不可能在几小时内完成
but nothing can happen in a few hours.
你就是想拖延时间好找到我们
You just want more time so you can find us.
我们在找你们吗  是的
Are we looking for you? Yes.
只是为保证你们把米勒一家毫发无伤地交出来
But that's only so you'll turn over the Millers without incident.
不会有什么移交
But there is no handing over.
要么满足我们的要求  否则他们就得死
Either you give us what we want or we kill them.
不证明他们还活着  我们什么都不会做
Nothing will happen until we have proof of life.
好吧  给你个活着的证据
All right, here's your proof of life.
把那女孩舌头割了
Cut out the girl's tongue.
-不  -我是康威
- No! - This is Conway.
-不  -请不要冲动
- No! - Please, before you do anything...
-妈妈  -约书  扎克
- Mommy! - Josh. Zach.
你以为我们在乎你知道我们的身份吗
Do you think we care you know who we are?
不  住手
No, stop!
我想跟你谈谈  一小会儿就行
I'd like to speak with you, just for a moment.
我有话要说
I... I have something to say,
但别让梅莉莎再叫了
but I need Melissa to stop screaming
-这样我才能听清你  -不
- so I can hear you. - No!
我能听听她说话吗
Can I hear her voice?
我们必须听见她说话
We need her voice.
我在这儿  我是梅莉莎
I'm here. I'm Melissa.
你好  梅莉莎  我是威尔
Hi, Melissa. My name is Will--
你听见她说话了  快说吧
You heard her voice. Now talk.
不
Oh, no.
对  我杀过很多人
Yes, I... I've killed a lot of people.
其中有无辜者
Some of them innocent people.
每一晚
And every single night...
我都没对我妻子说过
I haven't even told my wife this...
但每一晚  我都做噩梦
but every single night, I have nightmares.
我想象我自己的女儿  莉莉
I picture my own daughter, Lily,
我的妻子  儿子
and my wife... and my son,
就像你说的那样
just like you described...
被炸飞
blown away.
死了
Gone.
你可以说我
Now, you could say that I...
我做噩梦是因为我做得不对
I have these demons because what I did was wrong
而你的动机是正义的
and that your cause is righteous.
但我当时也认为我的动机是正义的
But I believed that my cause was righteous, too.
如果能撤销发生的事
And if I could take it all back...
我不会做同样的事
I wouldn't do it again.
其实
The truth is...
我为我的行为感到羞耻
I'm ashamed of what I've done.
总统说得对
Now, the president is right.
我们需要更多时间来筹备你们的要求
We need more time to work on your demands,
但更重要的是
but more importantly,
我猜你之前从没杀过人
I'm guessing you've never killed anyone before.
身为一个了解杀戮的人  我要说
And speaking as someone who knows what it means to kill,
在做出无法挽回之事前
you owe yourselves more time
你该给自己更多时间
before you do something you can never take back.
约书
Josh?
早九点  你们的最后期限
9:00 a.m. You have till then.
他们结束通话了
They've ended the call.
你做得非常好  州长
You did an excellent job, Governor.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们有一通战况室电话的录音
We have a recording of the Situation Room call
是由劫持者在不久前放出的
released by the captors a short while ago.
在播放音频之前  我们想提醒听众们
Before playing this audio, we want to warn viewers
其中部分内容会令人不安
that there are sections that are very disturbing.
建议大家把电视静音
You might want to mute the television.
人都哪去了
Where is everybody?
他们都去忙劫持的报导了
They all got pulled on the hostage story.
把他们叫回来
Get 'em back here.
还有玛姬·蒂尔顿
And Maggie Tilden, too.
转录  马上做
Transcribe this, right away.
查塔努加市外方圆50英里范围内
Fifty mile radius outside of Chattanooga.
用偷来的信用卡买汽油
Gas purchase on a stolen credit card.
马斯特森的同学之一
One of Masterson's classmates.
我们现在要放出他们的照片吗
Should we just release their photographs at this point?
我的电话被打爆了
I'm getting bombarded with calls.
州长用的是名字
Well, the governor used the first names.
会有人把线索拼凑起来的
Someone's gonna put it together.
-我们不如利用这一点  -先生
- We might as well exploit it. - Sir.
-乔治  -总统先生
- George. - Mr. President.
通常  我会给你时间重新考虑
Normally, I'd give you time to reconsider,
但今天时间太紧
but time is in short supply today.
不行  我不能这么对党派
I can't. Not to my party.
党会撑下去的
The party will survive.
康威也许不能  没办法  他撒谎了
Conway might not, but too bad. He lied.
如果我这么对他  我就撑不过去了
If I do this to him, I don't survive.
我会被鄙视
I'm vilified.
我想给你看点东西
I wanna show you something.
你知道这是什么吗
Do you know what this is?
这是我做党鞭时
This is your magnet
你在投票记数板上的磁铁名牌
from the vote count board when I used to be whip.
曾有很多次
There were so many times when
你不在我希望你在的位置  乔治
you weren't in the column I wanted you to be in, George.
我们都知道  我那时有几十次
And we both know that I could've forced you
可以逼你按照我的意愿投票
to vote the way I wanted you to dozens of times,
但我从没那么做过  我克制住了
but I never did. I held back.
是为了保护你的名誉
To protect your honor.
做党鞭的好处之一
And one of the advantages of being whip
就是每个党员
is that behind every single member,
每块磁铁名牌之后
behind all of these magnets,
都至少有一件不光彩的事
was at least one dishonorable thing.
只不过你的事恰好比大多数人都更不光彩
Yours just happens to be more dishonorable than most.
所以这次我要把你放在我那一栏里  乔治
So I'm putting you in my column this time, George.
莉安告诉我你在这儿
LeAnn told me you were in here.
我在写你的声明
I'm working on your statements,
为最坏的情况做准备
in case the worst happens.
真是紧张  这个地方
It's tense, this building.
墙壁里都透着这气息
You can feel it in the walls.
我早些时候去散步
I went for a walk earlier.
空气里都弥漫着紧张
It was in the air.
人们交谈都轻声低语
People were talking in whispers,
虽然完全没有必要这样
even though there was no reason to.
要不就两眼盯着手机
Or their eyes are glued to their phones.
没有孩子在外面玩耍
And there are no children out...
一个都没有
anywhere.
我想称之为恐怖是有原因的
I guess they call it terror for a reason.
比恐怖更糟  是恐惧
Worse than terror. Dread.
人们因一场悲剧把自己束缚起来
People girding themselves for a tragedy.
也可能反过来
Mmm, and it could go the other way.
你怎么样
How are you holding up?
汉娜在照看她的孩子
Hannah is minding her children.
我在照看她
I'm minding her.
她丈夫的表现真是出色  是吧
Her husband really knocked it out of the ballpark, huh?
你觉得他说的是真心的吗
Do you think anything he says is genuine?
这不重要  不是吗
Doesn't matter, does it?
起作用了就好
It worked.
你曾经说你觉得康威只会表面功夫
You said once you thought he was all surface, Conway.
是啊  自恋狂
Yeah, a narcissist.
但如果给他一滩水照照自己
But give him a pool to reflect in...
就要当心了
Watch out.
该怎么做  他清楚得很
He knows exactly what to do with that.
除非他弄巧成拙
Unless he overreaches.
你就希望如此吗
Is that what you were hoping?
希望他把这事搞砸吗
That he was gonna fuck it up?
因为他不会搞砸的
Because he's not gonna fuck it up.
他太聪明了
He's too smart for that.
"他升到空中
"There he soared,
从大本钟和伦敦眼旁边呼啸而过
zipping past Big Ben and the London Eye,
又从白金汉宫和皮卡迪利广场上方飞过
over Buckingham Palace and Piccadilly Circus.
看  他远去了"
Look at him go."
我马上回来  查理
I'll be right back, Charlie.
守夜的气氛特别阴沉
... the vigil is especially somber,
但上午早些时候达成的延期
but there remains a great deal of hope
还是带来了不少希望
after the deadline was extended earlier this morning.
-很多人将延期归功于州长  -情况如何
- Many credit that extension to Governor... - What's the latest?
有进展  搜索范围缩小了
Progress. They've narrowed the search zone.
通话中  可以听见梅莉莎在尖叫
During the call, Melissa could be heard screaming
因为马斯特森让霍松"割掉..."
as Masterson orders Hawthorne to, quote, "Cut out..."
水槽左边
Left of the sink.
此时康威州长介入
That's when Governor Conway stepped in.
抱歉  你也来一瓶吗
Oh, I'm sorry. You want one?
不了  谢谢
No, thank you.
现在我们播放他说的部分内容
We're going to play some of what he said right now.
-因为你的肝吗  -对  我...
- Is it your liver? - Yes, I...
-保持清醒  -我杀过很多人
- Clear mind. - I've killed a lot of people.
其中有无辜者
Some of them innocent people.
每一晚...
And every--
为什么关掉
Oh, why'd you turn it off?
我当时就在旁边
I was there.
一定让你很抓狂吧
That's gotta drive you crazy, huh?
我这下要有多少正面报道了
How much good press I'm getting out of this.
-什么这么好笑  -没什么
- What's funny? - Nothing.
告诉我吧  我也想听笑话
Come on, tell me. I want in on the joke.
你以为你能激怒我
You think you can get under my skin.
我们第一次见面时  我就激怒你了
Oh, I got under your skin the first time we met.
什么时候  新年前夜吗
When? New Year's?
我记得我那晚恭维了你
I believe I complimented you that night.
但你尽可以
But you go ahead,
为了摆出更高的姿态
you tell yourself what you have to
自欺欺人
in order to stand a little taller.
我真为你难过
I feel sorry for you.
两年
Two years.
你只能待这么点时间
That's all you're gonna get in here.
你在任的时间不会比沃克长
You're not gonna last any longer than Walker did.
最让你难受的  是我会做个了不起的总统
And what kills you is that I'll make a great president.
真正会被铭记的总统
The kind of president who'll actually be remembered.
那不是比死还让你难受吗  弗兰克
And isn't that worse than dying, Frank?
被遗忘
Being forgotten.
你还真以为你会是个了不起的总统
You actually think you'd make a great president.
今天只是小试牛刀
Today was just a little taste.
总统99%的工作是不为人知的
99% of this job is in the dark.
你今天在阳光下闪耀了一会儿
I mean, you had your little moment in the sun today,
但当你要做无数个
but what are you gonna do
永远无人知晓  无人感激的决定时
when you have to make a thousand decisions that no one will
你要怎么办呢
ever hear about or appreciate?
我觉得你很擅长竞选总统
I think you're excellent at running for the president,
但我不认为你真有能力做总统
but I don't think you're equipped to actually be one.
别这么居高临下
Don't be condescending.
我是纽约州长
I'm the Governor of New York.
奥尔巴尼  是吗
Ooh, Albany, really?
你是个冒牌货  威尔
You're a pretender, Will.
而如果你赢了
And if you win,
你就从冒牌货成了骗子
you'll go from pretender to fraud.
威尔
Will?
我要让孩子们睡觉了
I'm putting the kids to bed.
那我不耽搁你了
Don't let me keep you.
-也许你该送他们回家  -还不到时候
- Maybe you should send them home. - No, not yet.
除了沃勒克还有别的打算吗
Do you have something else in mind besides Walleck?
有  而且我需要你帮我
Yes, and I'll need your help.
查理  你看见他了吗
Charlie? Have you seen him?
查理
Charlie?
妈妈  你看我找到了什么
Mommy, look what I found!
快瞧瞧
Oh, look at those.
还给我  你不能玩这个
Give those back. Those aren't yours to play with.
-我能留着吗  -快还回去  查理
- Can I keep them? - Oh, um, hand them over, Charlie.
-查尔斯  -要不这样吧
- Charles. - No, you know what?
你还是留着吧
You should keep them,
因为你这一生就应该顺心如意
because you should get everything you want in this life.
快说谢谢
Um, say thank you.
-谢谢你  -应该谢谢你才是
- Thank you. - No, thank you
多谢你来白宫看我们
for coming to the White House to visit us.
我们都休息吧  明早七点见
We should get some rest. I'll see you at 7:00.
那时候我早就起了
Oh, I'll be up way before then.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
晚安
Good night.
我怎么帮你
You need my help how?
-还有谁知道  -没人了
- Who else knows about this? - No one.
我需要你尽快安排
I'll need you to make arrangements as quietly as possible.
好  我去办
All right, I'm on it.
我拿到地址之后马上告诉你
I'll let you know as soon as I have a location.
好  回家睡几个小时吧
Good. Then go home and get a few hours of sleep.
我今晚可睡不着
I can't sleep tonight.
试试吧  我们需要你明早精力充足
You should try. We'll need you fresh in the morning.
-联系参联会主席  -好的
- Get me the Chairman Joint Chiefs. - Yes, sir.
他在线上了  先生
He's on the line, sir.
主席先生
Mr. Chairman.
你想什么时候联系白宫
When do you wanna reach out to the White House?
明天  邮件我已经写好了
Tomorrow. I've drafted the email.
-你已经检查过了吗  -是的
- You looked this over? - Yes.
法律上我们没有问题
We're okay on the legal front.
但我们不该等人质危机结束吗
But shouldn't we wait until this crisis is over first?
绝不  这是我们的绝佳机会
No. This is perfect timing for us.
汤姆说得对  趁他不备  攻他不意
Tom's right. Let's hit him while he's distracted.
怎么样
How is it?
很好吃
Perfect.
你冰箱里实在是没什么可做的
Well, you didn't have much to work with in your fridge.
你得去买点吃的了
You need to do some grocery shopping.
-我不常做饭  -看出来了
- I don't cook a lot. - Obviously.
你需要的话就回去照顾孩子吧
If you have to get back to your kids...
没事
No, it's fine.
哈莉16岁了  有需要的话她会打给我的
Haley's 16. She'll call me if she needs anything.
他们看新闻了吗
Have they been watching the news?
看了  他们吓坏了
Yeah... and they're freaked out by it.
谁不怕呢  但是他们现在承受能力强多了
I mean, who isn't? But they've got thick skin by now.
比他们的同龄伙伴们镇静多了
Handling it a lot better than some of their friends.
我知道有好多父母
I know a lot of parents aren't
明天甚至都不打算让孩子出门了
even letting their kids out of the house tomorrow.
连学也不上了
Not even to go to school.
不过我的孩子还是会去的
My kids are gonna go, though.
我不会让这些畜生毁了我们的生活
I'm not gonna let these monsters rule over our lives.
-多谢你过来  -客气
- Thanks for coming over. - Of course.
我就算躺床上也只会盯着天花板发呆
I know I'd just be staring at the ceiling if I tried to sleep.
你的工作太繁重了
Well, you have a lot on your shoulders.
一般我会去参加个互助会什么的
Yeah, normally, I'd go to a meeting.
我只是...
I... I just, uh...
你只是希望能有人照顾你
You just wanted someone to take care of you.
能照顾别人也挺好的
And it's nice to take care of someone.
早上好  州长
Good morning, Governor.
你的电话
Your phone.
喂
Hello?
我们拍到一辆车
We have video of a car
在佐治亚州查茨沃思附近一十字路口处
at an intersection near Chatsworth, Georgia.
电话背景音里有鸟叫声
The bird song, deep background from the phone call,
说明他们在林区  南蓝岭
puts them in a wooded area. Southern Blue Ridge.
我们已经开始搜索了
We started canvassing now.
联调局  州警
FBI, state troopers.
电话连线了
The line is open.
好的  我的对话脚本呢
Uh, okay. Where... where's my script?
我来交涉
I'll be doing the talking.
需要你加入的时候我再告诉你
I'll let you know if I want you to participate.
先生  如果绑匪和州长之间
Sir, if we've established a dialogue
已经建立了对话  那我们应该...
between the kidnappers and the governor, we should--
接通吧
Start the call.
与人们印象中的"不与恐怖分子谈判"不同
美国政府处理人质绑架事件的原则实际上是
"不妥协  不让步"
就是说  美国政府未必不会与恐怖分子或恐怖组织
就人质问题进行协商
2015年6月  奥巴马政府通过总统行政命令的形式
进一步修改和明确了相关政策
允许美国政府官员代表人质家属同绑架者进行协商
但是法律仍然规定  美国政府不会向绑架者支付赎金
很多时候  "谈判"的界限在这种协商和交流中被模糊
有时候  美国政府也会为特定人质的获释付出很大代价
最近的一则例子  发生在2016年1月
三名美国公民在伊拉克被绑架
经调查  绑架者为当地什叶派军事武装人员
背后有伊朗支持
事发后  美国政府向伊拉克政府寻求帮助
在伊拉克情报机构和军方的斡旋下
三名人质于一个月后被释放
美国政府称  在寻求人质释放的过程中
他们没有直接同绑架者接触
但具体的谈判过程  绑架者是否得到赎金  外界不得而知
另一桩引起广泛关注的绑架案  涉及一名美国现役军人
2009年  美军士兵鲍尔·伯格道在阿富汗前线失踪
后确认被塔利班绑架
美军曾经组织多次营救行动  但均未成功
有特种兵战士在营救任务中阵亡
经过美国政府同塔利班的长期谈判
2014年5月31日  伯格道被塔利班释放
美国总统奥巴马亲自在白宫宣布了这一消息
作为交换  美国释放了五名被关押在关塔那摩监狱的塔利班囚犯
据媒体报道  这五名囚犯被俘前均在塔利班武装中担任重要职务
伯格道获释后  他的一些战友向媒体透露
他是擅自离开前线后被塔利班俘获的  是一名逃兵
部分美国国会成员和媒体对奥巴马政府
用五名高危恐怖分子换取一名"逃兵"的行为非常不满
白宫因此承受了很大压力
目前伯格道因叛逃罪正在接受军事法庭的审判